[
  {
    "question": "Who scored the first goal in the match?",
    "choices": [
      "A. Roberto Firmino",
      "B. Emre Can",
      "C. Philippe Coutinho",
      "D. Glenn Murray"
    ],
    "answer": "B",
    "type": "past",
    "question_level": "player",
    "related_event_index": [
      2
    ],
    "current_event_index": 2,
    "index": 0,
    "event_type": "goal"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which team scored more goals in the first half?",
    "choices": [
      "A. Liverpool",
      "B. Brighton",
      "C. Both teams scored equally",
      "D. No goals in the first half"
    ],
    "answer": "A",
    "type": "past",
    "question_level": "team",
    "related_event_index": [
      2,
      3
    ],
    "current_event_index": 3,
    "index": 1,
    "event_type": "goal"
  },
  {
    "question": "How many goals did Roberto Firmino score by the end of the match?",
    "choices": [
      "A. 1",
      "B. 2",
      "C. 3",
      "D. 4"
    ],
    "answer": "B",
    "type": "full",
    "question_level": "player",
    "related_event_index": [
      3,
      4
    ],
    "current_event_index": null,
    "index": 2,
    "event_type": "goal"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which player scored the last goal for Liverpool?",
    "choices": [
      "A. Roberto Firmino",
      "B. Emre Can",
      "C. Philippe Coutinho",
      "D. Mohamed Salah"
    ],
    "answer": "C",
    "type": "full",
    "question_level": "player",
    "related_event_index": [
      14
    ],
    "current_event_index": null,
    "index": 3,
    "event_type": "goal"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which team had the most goals in the match?",
    "choices": [
      "A. Liverpool",
      "B. Brighton",
      "C. Both teams scored equally",
      "D. No goals in the match"
    ],
    "answer": "A",
    "type": "full",
    "question_level": "team",
    "related_event_index": [
      2,
      3,
      4,
      7,
      14,
      16
    ],
    "current_event_index": null,
    "index": 4,
    "event_type": "goal"
  },
  {
    "question": "Will there be more goals after the 2nd half - 05:45 mark?",
    "choices": [
      "A. Yes",
      "B. No",
      "C. Only one more goal",
      "D. Two more goals"
    ],
    "answer": "A",
    "type": "future",
    "question_level": "match",
    "related_event_index": [
      14,
      16
    ],
    "current_event_index": 7,
    "index": 5,
    "event_type": "goal"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which player is most likely to score next after the 2nd half - 02:50 mark?",
    "choices": [
      "A. Roberto Firmino",
      "B. Philippe Coutinho",
      "C. Glenn Murray",
      "D. Lewis Dunk"
    ],
    "answer": "C",
    "type": "future",
    "question_level": "player",
    "related_event_index": [
      7
    ],
    "current_event_index": 4,
    "index": 6,
    "event_type": "goal"
  },
  {
    "question": "Will Liverpool score another goal after the 2nd half - 41:31 mark?",
    "choices": [
      "A. Yes",
      "B. No",
      "C. Only an own goal",
      "D. Two more goals"
    ],
    "answer": "B",
    "type": "future",
    "question_level": "team",
    "related_event_index": [],
    "current_event_index": 14,
    "index": 7,
    "event_type": "goal"
  },
  {
    "question": "How many yellow cards have occurred so far?",
    "choices": [
      "A. 0",
      "B. 1",
      "C. 2",
      "D. 3"
    ],
    "answer": "B",
    "type": "past",
    "question_level": "match",
    "related_event_index": [
      9
    ],
    "current_event_index": 9,
    "index": 0,
    "event_type": "yellow card"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which team has received more yellow cards up to now?",
    "choices": [
      "A. Brighton",
      "B. Opponent Team",
      "C. Both teams have equal",
      "D. No cards yet"
    ],
    "answer": "A",
    "type": "past",
    "question_level": "team",
    "related_event_index": [
      9
    ],
    "current_event_index": 9,
    "index": 1,
    "event_type": "yellow card"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which player received the last yellow card?",
    "choices": [
      "A. Bruno Saltor",
      "B. Player X",
      "C. Player Y",
      "D. No cards yet"
    ],
    "answer": "A",
    "type": "past",
    "question_level": "player",
    "related_event_index": [
      9
    ],
    "current_event_index": 9,
    "index": 2,
    "event_type": "yellow card"
  },
  {
    "question": "How many total yellow cards occurred in the match?",
    "choices": [
      "A. 0",
      "B. 1",
      "C. 2",
      "D. 3"
    ],
    "answer": "B",
    "type": "full",
    "question_level": "match",
    "related_event_index": [
      9
    ],
    "current_event_index": null,
    "index": 3,
    "event_type": "yellow card"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which team had the most yellow cards in the match?",
    "choices": [
      "A. Brighton",
      "B. Opponent Team",
      "C. Both teams have equal",
      "D. No cards"
    ],
    "answer": "A",
    "type": "full",
    "question_level": "team",
    "related_event_index": [
      9
    ],
    "current_event_index": null,
    "index": 4,
    "event_type": "yellow card"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which player was involved in the most yellow cards?",
    "choices": [
      "A. Bruno Saltor",
      "B. Player X",
      "C. Player Y",
      "D. No cards"
    ],
    "answer": "A",
    "type": "full",
    "question_level": "player",
    "related_event_index": [
      9
    ],
    "current_event_index": null,
    "index": 5,
    "event_type": "yellow card"
  },
  {
    "question": "Will there be more yellow cards in this match?",
    "choices": [
      "A. Yes",
      "B. No",
      "C. Maybe",
      "D. Not sure"
    ],
    "answer": "B",
    "type": "future",
    "question_level": "match",
    "related_event_index": [],
    "current_event_index": 9,
    "index": 6,
    "event_type": "yellow card"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which team is more likely to get the next yellow card?",
    "choices": [
      "A. Brighton",
      "B. Opponent Team",
      "C. Both teams",
      "D. Neither"
    ],
    "answer": "D",
    "type": "future",
    "question_level": "team",
    "related_event_index": [],
    "current_event_index": 9,
    "index": 7,
    "event_type": "yellow card"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which player is most likely to be involved in the next yellow card?",
    "choices": [
      "A. Bruno Saltor",
      "B. Player X",
      "C. Player Y",
      "D. No one"
    ],
    "answer": "D",
    "type": "future",
    "question_level": "player",
    "related_event_index": [],
    "current_event_index": 9,
    "index": 8,
    "event_type": "yellow card"
  },
  {
    "question": "How many corners have occurred so far?",
    "choices": [
      "A. 1",
      "B. 2",
      "C. 3",
      "D. 4"
    ],
    "answer": "B",
    "type": "past",
    "question_level": "match",
    "related_event_index": [
      0,
      1
    ],
    "current_event_index": 1,
    "index": 0,
    "event_type": "corner"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which team has taken more corners up to now?",
    "choices": [
      "A. Liverpool",
      "B. Brighton",
      "C. Both teams have taken the same number",
      "D. Neither team has taken a corner"
    ],
    "answer": "A",
    "type": "past",
    "question_level": "team",
    "related_event_index": [
      0,
      1
    ],
    "current_event_index": 1,
    "index": 1,
    "event_type": "corner"
  },
  {
    "question": "Who took the last corner kick?",
    "choices": [
      "A. Mohamed Salah",
      "B. Philippe Coutinho",
      "C. Pascal Gross",
      "D. None of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "B",
    "type": "past",
    "question_level": "player",
    "related_event_index": [
      1
    ],
    "current_event_index": 1,
    "index": 2,
    "event_type": "corner"
  },
  {
    "question": "How many total corners occurred in the match?",
    "choices": [
      "A. 2",
      "B. 3",
      "C. 4",
      "D. 5"
    ],
    "answer": "C",
    "type": "full",
    "question_level": "match",
    "related_event_index": [
      0,
      1,
      5,
      8
    ],
    "current_event_index": null,
    "index": 3,
    "event_type": "corner"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which team had the most corners in the match?",
    "choices": [
      "A. Liverpool",
      "B. Brighton",
      "C. Both teams had the same number",
      "D. Neither team had a corner"
    ],
    "answer": "C",
    "type": "full",
    "question_level": "team",
    "related_event_index": [
      0,
      1,
      5,
      8
    ],
    "current_event_index": null,
    "index": 4,
    "event_type": "corner"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which player was involved in the most corners?",
    "choices": [
      "A. Mohamed Salah",
      "B. Philippe Coutinho",
      "C. Pascal Gross",
      "D. None of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "C",
    "type": "full",
    "question_level": "player",
    "related_event_index": [
      0,
      1,
      5,
      8
    ],
    "current_event_index": null,
    "index": 5,
    "event_type": "corner"
  },
  {
    "question": "Will there be more corners in this match?",
    "choices": [
      "A. Yes",
      "B. No",
      "C. Only one more",
      "D. Two more"
    ],
    "answer": "A",
    "type": "future",
    "question_level": "match",
    "related_event_index": [
      5,
      8
    ],
    "current_event_index": 1,
    "index": 6,
    "event_type": "corner"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which team is more likely to get the next corner?",
    "choices": [
      "A. Liverpool",
      "B. Brighton",
      "C. Both teams are equally likely",
      "D. Neither team will get another corner"
    ],
    "answer": "B",
    "type": "future",
    "question_level": "team",
    "related_event_index": [
      5,
      8
    ],
    "current_event_index": 1,
    "index": 7,
    "event_type": "corner"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which player is most likely to be involved in the next corner?",
    "choices": [
      "A. Mohamed Salah",
      "B. Philippe Coutinho",
      "C. Pascal Gross",
      "D. None of the above"
    ],
    "answer": "C",
    "type": "future",
    "question_level": "player",
    "related_event_index": [
      5,
      8
    ],
    "current_event_index": 1,
    "index": 8,
    "event_type": "corner"
  }
]